http://www.ooks.com/privacy-policy.html

855-270-OOKS (6657)
OOKinfo@hillmangroup.comContactSite MapLogin
HomeAbout UsOnline StoreHang Like A ProRequest InformationOOK TV
Online StorePicture HangersWireFrame BacksSpecialty Hooks
& Hangers
Tweet
Privacy Policy
The Hillman Group, Inc. and its affiliated companies (“The Hillman Group”) respect your privacy and the purpose for which our website visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information CollectedIf you request or submit information to us by sending an e-mail via the "mail to:" function or filling out a "contact" form, we may save your e-mail address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, e-mail, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your e-mail and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by OthersThis notice addresses only the policy of The Hillman Group's website and not sites that users access via links from our website. The Hillman Group is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
CookiesThe Hillman Group website does not use cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal InformationIf you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an e-mail with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of InformationThe Hillman Group may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy ChangesPlease note that The Hillman Group reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of The Hillman Group. This statement does not create an agreement between The Hillman Group and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party. If you choose to visit our website, your visit and any dispute over privacy are subject to this privacy policy and the laws of the State of Ohio.
Contact UsThe Hillman Group10590 Hamilton AvenueCincinnati, OH 45231Toll-Free: 1.800.800.4900Fax: 513.851.4997E-mail: info@hillmangroup.com
Print This PageEmail This Page
Home|About Us|Online Store|HANG LIKE A PRO|Request Information|OOK TV|Return Policy1590 NW 27th Avenue, #9 Pompano Beach, Florida 33069  |  Toll Free Ph: 855-270-OOKS (6657)  |  Toll Free Fax: 800-582-6110
© 2012 OOK®  |  Hillman Group  |  Privacy  |  Site Map  |  All rights reserved. Any usage of the images contained herein is strictly forbidden without the prior written consent of The Hillman Group, Inc.
